COFFEY MAY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

SKILLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript | ES6
- ReactJS
- C#
- Sass
- NodeJS
- Express
- MongoDb
- SQL
- Bootstrap CSS
- ASP.NET Core
- Postman
- Material UI
- Git/Github
- Photoshop
- Figma
- Visual Studio
- Visual Studio Code

CONTACT

- 615-474-8498
- JCOFFEYMAY6@GMAIL.COM
- WWW.LINKEDIN.COM /IN/JONATHANCOFFEYMAY/
- GITHUB.COM/COFFEY-MAY
- COFFEYMAYDEV.COM

ABOUT ME

As a recent graduate of the Nashville Software School, I am eager to apply my training as a Full Stack Software Developer. As an entry-level or junior programmer, I hope to hone, refine, and expand the skills that I have been cultivating in the two years of experience that I have with coding. I am also eager to join a team and further develop my experience with agile methodologies, larger codebases, and emerging technologies.

EDUCATION

NASHVILLE SOFTWARE SCHOOL

2019 - 2020 | CERTIFICATE DEGREE IN FULL STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

Comprehensive, 6 month software development program with a concentration on full-stack technology training. The development of software applications in individual and agile team environments, as well up to date development practices in a multitude of technologies. Git and GitHub utilized for version control, use of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React,JS and C# for the development of front and backend development projects.

WATKINS COLLEGE OF ART AND DESIGN

2003-2007 | BACHELORS OF FINE ART

Formal instruction in 2-D design, sculpture, graphic design, multimedia, art history, and web design. 4 year liberal arts education with emphasis on critical theory and contemporary art.

WORK HISTORY

2001 -2020 SERVER

Customer Service and sales at food service industry.

- Noshville Delicatessen | 2001–2015
- Sambuca | 2015-2017
- Table3 | 2017-2019
- Union Common | 2019-2020

2008-PRESENT

PHOTO-REALIST OIL PAINTER

Various oil painting commissions for private Clients and Collections including the Catholic Diocese of Nashville. Techniques ranging from Classical, Dutch, Contemporary.

PORTFOLIO

coffeymaydev.com

This Portfolio site contains numerous projects that demonstrate a wide range of my abilities. Built using ReactJS, this site and the corresponding projects therein showcase my ability to dynamically render data, perform async api calls, manage state on the client side via Redux as well as server side via NodeJS. This project demonstrates CRUD operations, utilizes numerous auth components, and manages user restrictions. My future works on this site intend to employ a C#/SQL server database component as well.